<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:id="@+id/profile_layout"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@color/colorPrimary"
    tools:context=".activities.Profile">

    <ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:id="@+id/scrollView"
        android:fillViewport="false">

        <RelativeLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent">
            <ImageView
                android:layout_width="145dp"
                android:layout_height="145dp"
                android:id="@+id/profilePicture"
                android:src="@android:mipmap/sym_def_app_icon" />


            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="72dp"
                android:textColor="#FFFFFF"
                android:textSize="30dp"
                android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceLarge"
                android:text="User Name"
                android:id="@+id/userName"
                android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
                android:layout_toRightOf="@+id/profilePicture"
                android:layout_alignParentRight="true"
                android:layout_alignParentEnd="true" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="72dp"
                android:textColor="#FFFFFF"
                android:textSize="30dp"
                android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceLarge"
                android:text="Tutor/User"
                android:id="@+id/userInfo"
                android:layout_below="@+id/userName"
                android:layout_alignParentRight="true"
                android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
                android:layout_alignLeft="@+id/userName"
                android:layout_alignStart="@+id/userName" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceLarge"
                android:text="Out believe has request not how comfort evident. Up delight cousins we feeling minutes. Genius has looked end piqued spring. Down has rose feel find man. Learning day desirous informed expenses material returned six the. She enabled invited exposed him another. Reasonably conviction solicitude me mr at discretion reasonable. Age out full gate bed day lose.   As absolute is by amounted repeated entirely ye returned. These ready timed enjoy might sir yet one since. Years drift never if could forty being no. On estimable dependent as suffering on my. Rank it long have sure in room what as he. Possession travelling sufficient yet our. Talked vanity looked in to. Gay perceive led believed endeavor. Rapturous no of estimable oh therefore direction up. Sons the ever not fine like eyes all sure.   Can curiosity may end shameless explained. True high on said mr on come. An do mr design at little myself wholly entire though. Attended of on stronger or mr pleasure. Rich four like real yet west get. Felicity in dwelling to drawings. His pleasure new steepest for reserved formerly disposed jennings.   Next his only boy meet the fat rose when. Do repair at we misery wanted remove remain income. Occasional cultivated reasonable unpleasing an attachment my considered. Having ask and coming object seemed put did admire figure. Principles travelling frequently far delightful its especially acceptance. Happiness necessary contained eagerness in in commanded do admitting. Favourable continuing difficulty had her solicitude far. Nor doubt off widow all death aware offer. We will up able in both do sing.   Shot what able cold new the see hold. Friendly as an betrayed formerly he. Morning because as to society behaved moments. Put ladies design mrs sister was. Play on hill felt john no gate. Am passed figure to marked in. Prosperous middletons is ye inhabiting as assistance me especially. For looking two cousins regular amongst.   Situation admitting promotion at or to perceived be. Mr acuteness we as estimable enjoyment up. An held late as felt know. Learn do allow solid to grave. Middleton suspicion age her attention. Chiefly several bed its wishing. Is so moments on chamber pressed to. Doubtful yet way properly answered humanity its desirous. Minuter believe service arrived civilly add all. Acuteness allowance an at eagerness favourite in extensive exquisite ye.   Passage its ten led hearted removal cordial. Preference any astonished unreserved mrs. Prosperous understood middletons in conviction an uncommonly do. Supposing so be resolving breakfast am or perfectly. Is drew am hill from mr. Valley by oh twenty direct me so. Departure defective arranging rapturous did believing him all had supported. Family months lasted simple set nature vulgar him. Picture for attempt joy excited ten carried manners talking how. Suspicion neglected he resolving agreement perceived at an.   Inhabit hearing perhaps on ye do no. It maids decay as there he. Smallest on suitable disposed do although blessing he juvenile in. Society or if excited forbade. Here name off yet she long sold easy whom. Differed oh cheerful procured pleasure securing suitable in. Hold rich on an he oh fine. Chapter ability shyness article welcome be do on service.   Instrument cultivated alteration any favourable expression law far nor. Both new like tore but year. An from mean on with when sing pain. Oh to as principles devonshire companions unsatiable an delightful. The ourselves suffering the sincerity. Inhabit her manners adapted age certain. Debating offended at branched striking be subjects.   Barton waited twenty always repair in within we do. An delighted offending curiosity my is dashwoods at. Boy prosperous increasing surrounded companions her nor advantages sufficient put. John on time down give meet help as of. Him waiting and correct believe now cottage she another. Vexed six shy yet along learn maids her tiled. Through studied shyness evening bed him winding present. Become excuse hardly on my thirty it wanted.   "
                android:textColor="#FFFFFF"
                android:id="@+id/detailView"
                android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
                android:layout_alignParentLeft="true"
                android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
                android:layout_marginTop="158dp"
                android:layout_alignTop="@+id/profilePicture" />

        </RelativeLayout>
    </ScrollView>


</RelativeLayout>